You don’t want it?
It’s very expensive.
No doubt. All you have is money.
Then why not accept it?
I'll throw it away.
Is it that cheap in your eyes?
Then throw it away.
You used the ring to embarrass me,
in front of that kind of girl.
I haven't broken up with Ji Hee.
Are you going to marry her, then?
Congratulations.
Is that you? Ji Hee, answer me.
Thank you for marrying me.
I love you.
- Yoo Jung, are you okay? - Yes.
What did we hit?
I don't know.
It's too dangerous. You stay here.
Do Hoon.
Listen to me. It's okay.
I told you to stay inside.
What was it?
- Thank god. - Let's get out of here.
Wait. Let's move it.
Other cars might hit it.
Are you her family member?
Her viscera are bleeding due to the hit.
Because she was left ignored for such a long time,
her liver and spleen have started hardening.
The biggest problem is the dead infant
that keeps putting pressure on her uterus.
She was pregnant?
Yes, what we need to do now
is to remove the fetus quickly.
Please, save her.
- Please. - I'll do my best.
Call Dr Park at once and get the O.R. ready.
What happend?
Kwang Soo. Find out exactly what happened.
Knead the dough gently, or it won't rise well.
I know.
That's not it. Step aside.
- Dad. - What?
I grew up playing with this.
How can a baker's daughter don't know how to bake?
The taste is more important than the shape.
You have a long way to go. You need to learn a lot.
So hot! Hot!
They look good.
Pay me first.
Dad, if you treat me this way,
you'll regret it after I get married.
The family in 305 is showing off
when the son opend a law firm.
It costs a lot of money.
Do Hoon, have a seat.
It's your first day to work, you must eat your fill.
Lawyers don't earn as much money as they used to do.
It's not easy to make money in the beginning.
Stop talking about money in such an early morning.
I'm not talking about money.
You can't make so much money as a prosecutor.
The country won't pay you too much.
I'm just proud that he finally make it
after paying the high tuition.
Son, a friend of your aunt Young Sook's cousin has a daughter.
She is a doctor, and she's preety and kind.
Enough.
Why are you yelling at me?
He's already given Yoo Jung the ring.
Why do you keeping on introducing him to others?
It's just a ring. They're not married, yet.
Then you tell me.
Who paid Do Hoon's tuition when we had no money?
Who pay the moeny for ancestral services every year?
She bought him a car, and paid for his insurance
When we almost lost this house because of your debt.
Who helped us out to keep this house?
I never asked her to do anything...
Should I break up with her?
Thank you for taking care of me.
I'm a prosecutor now,
and I'll marry someone with a better background.
Is that what you want?
No, you can't do this.
Mother. Don't turn me into a bad guy.
Do Hoon! You should have breakfast!
At least eat the egg.
Come on.
Prosecutor! My prosecutor son.
Have a good day.
I love you.
Stop! You'll bother others.
Your Honor, take care.
Did you witness the accident?
No.
I didn't witness it.
Wasn't there a surveillance camera?
There were no surveillance cameras at the scene.
There are cameras near the scene.
We're looking at the cars that entered the area,
but there are too many of them.
So you have the list of the cars, then?
We're still investigating that.
Please help me.
Wow!
Father!
Yoo Jung!
Why do you come over here at this time?
I work the afternoon shift.
Take this as a snack.
I baked it this morning.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
By the way, where is the car key?
Here it is.
What for?
I'm going to get the car fixed.
There's something wrong with the wipers.
Just ask Do Hoon to fix it.
Today is his first day of work, he must be busy.
I don't wnat to bother him.
I'll see you later.
Yoo Jung.
Do Hoon told me.
Thank you for making me your father-in-law.
The wipers are broken.
150000 KRW isn't enough.
They'll charge you at least 500000KRW at a garage.
That's why I came to you.
You said you used to run a garage.
You can fix it.
Even if I could get secondhand parts, it'd cost me over 150000 KRW.
170000 KRW.
No.
I baked it myself.
You said you like the bread I baked.
Come on. Ah.
Delicious.
I checked the traffic cameras near the accident scene.
Get to the point. Have you found it?
I've narrowed it down to 3 cars.
Who is she?
You're still drunk.
You can't drive. Give me the keys.
Not only do you have no respect for money, but you have no respect for others, either.
The customer is always right.
You should listen to the customer.
Ms. Seo Ji Hee's guardian please come to the ICU right away.
No.
Ji Hee.
Wait.
Are you okay?
What happend to her?
Our baby.
Ji Hee, it'll be okay.
I love you.
What did you say?
Ji Hee!
Ji Hee! Open your eyes!
Seo Ji Hee, 25 years old. Time of death, 3:57.
I told you to save her.
I told you to save her. Bastard!
Let go of me! I said let go.
It's your first day. Don't work too hard.
- I'm not working. - Aren't you tired of reading precedent cases?
- It's not good to be too honest. Let's go. - Where are we going?
We're having a welcome dinner for you.
Have you finished the building?
Yes. I stayed in Hong Kong to supervise it.
A valuable building is even better than a person.
- Se Yeon, are you back for good from France? - Yes.
Are you really getting married?
Marry? Your mother opened up an art gallery.
I thought you come back to help her.
Jo Min Hyuk, right?
Nothing's for sure yet.
Our parents are discussing the matter.
Lots of celebrity girls come to Jo Min Hyuk's parties.
I came across Hong Jung Ah ar the shopping mall, she regards herself as Min Hyuk's girlfriend.
Hong Jung Ah? She's over the hill.
No taste.
Did you enjoy the show?
I guess you're having a bad day as well.
Thank you for coming.
Are you an acquaintance of my daughter?
She's my friend.
What are you doing?
- Is this your car? - Yes.
- Ms. Kang Yoo Jung? - Yes.
Between 10 p.m. and 11 p.m. on the 23rd,
were you on the No. 8 National Road?
Were you driving yourself?
I seemed to hit something.
I don't want to make things complicated. I just broke the bumper.
I was driving. What's going on?
- It's a hit-and-run case. - A hit-and-run? - Yes.
What do you mean?
The new musical will be held next month.
I hope lots of people will come. That'll boost the morale of the performers.
Arragnge some seats to congressmen.
Egg plant is good when it's hot. Have some.
Min Hyuk, where were you the whole night?
Ji Hee is dead.
Steward, sprinkle some salt here.
I don't want a ghost in my house.
I get it. Even though she's dead, I can't be with her?
I like the way you look at me.
If you lose something, you'll earn something.
That's why I lost my mother, right?
Min Hyuk, how can you talk to your father like that.
Go to your room.
Why don't you stay out of it?
- This is our family matter. - Min Hyuk!
Get out and leave us alone.
When you were young, your puppy died, you cried for a while.
I bought you a car,
and you forgot about the dog.
How old are you?
You're a little too old for crying over a toy.
What about you?
You needed a new toy,
so you live with her?
Get out! Make your own money,
and do whatever you want to do.
You've never made a penny on your own.
You want freedom?
You'll realize that the freedom is given by me.
- This is the case assigned to you. - Okay.
Hello, prosecutor Ahn.
- Have you had lunch yet? - Yes.
How do you feel about your first case?
I'm nervous.
Don't be nervous. The police will sue the defendant.
The evidence is conclusive.
- Just take it. - Okay.
You're being too kind to him for his first case.
It's so easy that he can definitely win.
You always assign me difficult cases.
Stop nagging.
Let's go. Keep it up.
Bye. About the case.
- Have they arrested the culprit? - Not yet.
It's a hit-and-run case.
I'm not saying that you did it.
We're investigating the cars that passed through the area at that time.
Thank you for your cooperation.
- Thank you. It'll be 7500KRW. - What are you doing?
Sorry, drive safely.
Dad.
Yuejeong. There's a letter for you.
What is it?
You're in the final list of the recipe contest.
Really?
We've got a lot of luck recently.
Read it again, dad.
You're in the final list of the recipe contest.
I'm so happy!
What are you doing here?
I was thinking about going to your place.
What happened?
Why didn't you tell me?
You just became a prosecutor.
I didn't want you to go to the police office.
You idiot.
Do you know how serious this case is?
The police said I was a witness.
They are investigating every car that passed that area.
A witness?
You're a main suspect in a hit-and-run case.
The victim has dead.
Dead?
What is this?
How come you're the driver here?
I'm the owner of the car.
So I said I drove the car that day.
Why did you fix the car?
I told you that I'd scrap it.
I told you that I'd take care of it.
Why did you do this?
You should've told me first.
I know how busy you are.
I didn't want to bother you.
You didn't even to go a garage.
I wanted to save some money.
I can explain everything.
They don't need your explanation.
They only believe what they see.
It doesn't make sense. How can we be criminals?
We were almost killed as well.
The truck came out of nowhere,
and we hit the truck.
We're victims as well.
That doesn't make us innocent.
Do Hoon.
Let's go tell them the truth.
This is just ridiculous.
Do Hoon, wait!
Let's go.
What's going to happen to you?
I'm the prosecutor of this case.
I'm not even allowed to see you under such circumstance.
I'll probably have to resign.
How could this happen?
I'm not going.
Do you remember the day we first met?
Do you remember the words you said?
Are you out of your mind?
Hey, you.
How can you put gasoline in a diesel car?
Didn't you see that?
Here you go. Thank you. Come again.
It's an expensive car. What are you going to do?
I was about to put diesel, but you asked me to put petrol.
I took a pity on you to let you work here.
Now you're lying to me.
I made a mistake, but I didn't lie.
How dare you yell at me?
You should apologize for your mistake.
Sorry.
What?
I'm sorry.
You should be sorry.
What are you going to do with this?
I'll deduct it from your salary every month.
You can't do that.
You know my situation.
I don't care about your situation.
I only care about my situation.
Accordign to the civil law, article 756,
the person who hired an employee,
is also responsible for paying
the damage imposed on a 3rd party
by his or her employee.
To put it simply, the owner is responsible for the damage.
There were cases that the owner pay for 20% of the damage.
Who are you?
I'm her boyfriend.
Excuse me. Thank you for helping me.
Why did you help me?
Do I need to have a reason to help others?
Why did you claim that you were my boyfriend?
If I hadn't, he would've told me to go away.
You could've told him that you were my brother.
We don't look alike.
Have you ever lost in any argument?
No.
You'll win all your cases when you become a prosecutor.
I hope so.
Would you help me when I were wronged in the future?
I'll definitely help those who have no money and no power.
What about those who have money and power?
They'll be able to take care of themselves.
What if you pretend that you don't know me?
Take this to go for me.
I'll help you.
You told me to come to you with this when I'm in trouble.
Help me.
I was worried that my boyfriend would be wrongfully accused of being involved in a hit-and-run.
So I said I was the driver.
Please help my boyfriend.
Yoo Jung.
Will you help me?
If you're prosecuted, you'll go to trial.
Something terrible could happen.
A hit-and-run driver would spend at least 5 years in prison.
Do you know what that means?
I trust you.
But...
You are so handsome.
You're so handsome to achive your dream step by step.
You've worked so hard to come this far.
I know that more than anyone.
You can't let all your efforts go waste due to a misunderstanding.
What about your dreams?
I need you to achieve my dreams.
I can wait a little longer.
But...
I love you.
More than myself.
I trust you.
You can trust me, right?
There must've been a mistake.
We know the truth.
You can protect me.
Min Hyuk, what's your dream?
Dream? I don't have one.
Everybody has a dream.
You're too lazy to think about it.
I'll take as much money as I can from my father,
I want to live my life in my way.
You're so bad.
My father used to know how to smile.
He's too rich, and now he's angry all the time.
I should take his money for his own sake.
What's your dream?
To die just one day earlier than you.
What?
I want to hold your hand when we are old,
go shopping and go to movies together,
I can put my hand in your pocket when it's cold.
When our grandchildren make a mess in our house, we can clean it up together.
Our daughter would be beautiful
if she looks like you.
She would be adorable.
That's easy.
Really? Can you do that for me?
Of course.
It's not hard as long as we get old together.
I was alomost dead.
You're home so late.
What do you think you're doing?
You're prentending to be cool.
What are you doing here?
You're my only friend.
What are these?
I don't know.
Why do you paint something
that you don't know?
I don't think about anything when I'm painting.
That's good.
Very good.
How come?
I don't even have a friend to turn to.
What a pathetic life!
I'm glad you've realized that now.
Do you really want to marry me?
If my father kicks me out,
and I become penniless,
will you marry me as well?
Do you remember when we went to school?
We wanted to play outside after school
just like other kids.
But there were reporters at the gate every day.
We skipped a class and went outside to play once.
Right, it was funny.
But I never wanted to do it again.
I suffered a lot to go home.
I had no money to take a bus.
My feet hurt so much after getting home.
I swore that I would never do it again.
If you were not the heir of K Corporation,
I would not marry you.
Typical Shin Se Yeon.
It's your style.
Don't you think that life sucks?
It's so boring.
Min Hyuk! Min Hyuk!
What are you doing?
Wake up!
What's wrong with you? Min Hyuk!
He doesn't even dare to commit a suicide.
So he took pills?
He learns nothing good
but it from his mother.
I've kept this informaiton in secret.
What about the media?
I made an announcement that he's been working too hard.
He was trying to commit a suicide.
If being exposed to the media, it would've been a disaster.
Se Yeon did a good job of dealing with the matter,
So it won't be that terrible.
He's my only son,
and he's an idiot.
Okay.
If he rests for a while, he'll be okay?
Yes.
By the way,
what about the hit-and-run case?
After checking the video,
the police are going to issue an arrest warrant for the suspect.
Really?
Wrap it up quickly
before the rumor gets out.
There're too many things to worry about his marriage,
I don't want to cause trouble due to that woman.
Min Hyuk has had his stomach pumped.
Luckily you found it quickly.
You must be startled.
No. I'm angry.
Why can't you be honest with your feelings?
You're a lot like Min Hyuk.
Do you know that Ji Hee's dead?
It was an accident.
She was so young.
Min Hyuk is so devastated.
What a bastard.
He came to die in front of me?
How dare he!
Se Yeon. If you like him,
don't pretend that you're strong.
It's easy to win a man's heart.
When he feels vulnerable, stay with him.
You should get rid of thorns when you buy roses.
Maybe that's how you live,
but I want to keep my dignity.
Mom.
Yes, I'm here. Are you okay?
Get out of my room.
I'll call your father.
Hello.
What?
Are you sure?
Min Hyuk, you haven't recoverd yet.
Leave me alone.
Then don't come to me.
Don't behave like that in front of me because that woman.
Leave me alone.
Pull yourself together.
I saved your life,
and you're trying to kill yourself again?
I'm okay now.
Thank you, Se Yeon.
For saving my life.
I just remembered what I have to do.
Ms. Kang, do you really think that you're making any sense?
I meant it. I didn't know.
If you didn't know,
why did you fix your car the next day
at a place, which isn't even a garage?
Don't you find it suspicious?
Because,
I want to get a discount from some one I know,
A discount.
We found blood,
on the car you took to the guy you know
for a discount.
Impossible, there must be something wrong.
Trust me.
No one was there.
I didn't see anybody.
A truck just jumped out in front of us,
and the car slipped,
and we... I...
I hit the drum
in the construction site nearby.
I got out of the car and checked myself.
The drum you said
wasn't at the scene of the accident.
I moved it to the side
so that no one else would get hurt.
Please, go check one more time.
I don't need to check.
We have evidence.
Do you think you can go away with it?
Anyway, We'll get the result from forensic report on the blood today.
No, this can't be true. I didn't know.
I didn't see anyone.
Oops!
I don't think you understand how serious it is.
The victim that you hit...
Are you listening to me?
Listen to me!
I'm talking about the victim who died.
Seo Ji Hee, 25 years old.
She was found at the scene,
and she was pregnant.
We found the medical diagnosis she got that afternoon.
Excuse me, where's the Traffic Accident Office?
That way.
Was that you?
You can't just hit people and run away.
Sorry.
If you're really sorry, show me how sorry you are.
It seems like you are here for a cse.
But I have no time to do this with you.
How dare you hurt my woman?
Hello.
I have found the surveillance camera at the accident scene.
I'll check now.
No, I'll check myself. Please wait.
Sorry can't deal with everything.
You know how sad I am?
Hey.
What's this?
What're you doing in the police office?
Let go.
Let her go.
Who are you?
Don't look at me with innocent eyes.
Detective Choi.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Wait!
The image isn't clear.
It's impossible to see who the driver is.
It took me a long time to find the license plate number.
What's this car?
If we find the black box from this car,
we might be able to find the drum that the defendant saw.
Sir, don't worry about the drum.
If we have the driver's face on the black box,
she won't be able to deny it any longer.
I just collect them from the hospital.
If the parents don't take them, the dead infant won't have a funeral.
The surgery was done on the 24th at Sodam Hospital.
I don't know.
Well.
Sodam Hospital.
Kwang Soo!
Yes.
Why do all the people that I love leave me like this?
What should I do?
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
Does the law of our country allow a murder walk around freely?
When did you start caring about the law?
Why are you so interested in a stranger's case?
She's not a stranger.
Who? Kang Yoo Jung?
What do you think will happen?
Rain erased most of the evidence,
but we found footsteps walking away from the victim,
they're hard to identify.
We could use it as proof that she left the victim there on purpose.
She saw the victim, yet she walked away.
Are you busy this afternoon?
What?
I need to ask you a favor.
I have a friend.
He's a complete jackass,
but I want to get along well with him.
He wants to see you.
Me?
I think he knows the victim in your case.
He wants to know a few things regarding the case.
He must be a very powerful man to pull strings like this.
He's the heir of the K Corporation.
The car is waiting outside.
I know it's awkward to ask you this.
You don't have to if you don't want to.
I'll go.
I'm curious what he wants to know.
Thank you.
Prosecutor Ahn,
I'll escort you.
Please wait here for a moment.
Have we ever met before?
Yes.
Attack.
He doesn't understand Korean. He was trained in Germany.
I hope you don't remember me.
Let's go.
You're a little different from Hyun Suk.
Have a seat.
Siblings?
No.
Are you married?
Not yet.
You seem bored. Do you have a girlfriend?
Is this a job interview?
This is Ahn Do Hoon, a prosecutor from the Seoul District Court.
Good to see you again.
She's my fiancee Shin Se Yeon.
I heard that you're interested in my case.
Okay, let's get to the point.
How many years can she get in this case?
That's not the reason why you wanted to see me.
I like the way you talk.
I heard that you have sufficient evidence for your case.
Why haven't you prosecuted the defendant yet?
It's an ongoing investigation, and we can't discuss it.
Really? Keep investigating.
Kang Yoo Jung. Make her suffer.
Can I ask you how you know Kang Yoo Jung?
I don't care who she is.
I care about the victim.
Seo Ji Hee.
She is the woman he loves most.
You must know because you're the prosecutor.
The victim...
I heard that she was pregnant.
Se Yeon, your mother's coming tonight. Stop drinking.
I have to go.
I haven't done my hair yet to take you here.
My mother will give me an earful.
Wait. I'll call a driver for you.
That's okay. Stop being nice. It's not like you.
Tell him about the girl that you loved so much.
I can't do you a favor simply because you asked me to.
I didn't ask you.
I want to see if you are a qualified prosecutor.
I'll drive.
Go away.
You had four glasses of wine.
Leave me alone.
I am worried about you.
Kwang Soo.
Yes.
Do a background check on him.
Next on Secret Love.
Take it easy.
Let's talk over drink.
Let's be friends.
Ms. Kang Yoo Jung, you're under arrest.
I sentence Kang Yoo Jung to jail for 5 years.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
You don't even know that you're pregnant.
Kang Yoo Jung is pregnant?
This is getting interesting.